[Music]
This video will be
helpful in your wealth creation process and
how helpful it is in your financial growth in the long
term. We will detail it in the video.
Welcome to Holistic Investment Strategy. It
helps individual investors to make the right financial decisions and also to make smart financial gains quickly.
We will first look at its basic structure. In
this plan,
you will
invest the premium amount in the market.
Single pay means starting
benefit. You can avail limited pay,
limited pay, premium pay, five
years, ten years. It will be convenient for you to pay premium for an amount of time.
After that, you can avail tax on the
policy. You can avail
returns on
regular pay. You
can avail positive returns on regular pay.
Minimum investment is 2 lakh and ATC.
Tax benefit up to Rs 1.5 lakh is available as per the calculation.
So, in this, we had said that we can invest in other funds.
We will
see what all we can do. Different
allocation of funds in different categories.  Funds are available, for
example, if you say you want to invest in 100% equity funds, then
such funds are
also available to you. If you want to invest in 100% equity
funds, then you can invest in funds
by moderating low and high.
And now, what about
investing in multiple funds, you can
invest in friends, multiple friends, and you
can switch off your phone.
And this is not the time for
Papa, this fund, this fund is only according to
your needs through
flexible disposal. So this is polythene. Because
how should these funds be, you
can invest according to your needs.
So we can say,
next, you will get all the features of the current fund, what is the top
up like cotton additional money, then
you can invest in this Paul Sharma and you will get
parcel withdrawal benefit in it, you will get
Loyalty Addition and Wealth Booster, you
can increase and decrease your SAM and there
are unlimited free switches plus policy
revival. Now, what features do we have?  Now we will see these false
benefits, not benefits, it
gives us two benefits and one is death benefit,
now we will see the depth
benefits, if the holder passes away then
unfortunately the false
nominee will get death benefit,
put three values ​​and what will be available in these three values,
for example, same next the
fan value like
choice of the total premium pay,
what positive benefit will we get in these values, let
us see with an example,
for example, let us take
this policy, K10
annual cream,
so for example, if the
rate of interest is 4.9 percent, now we can say that we will get
4% net return, so if because
of the hidden charger, then
5% annual premium
charges are also levied in it,
look carefully, it was of
4.97%, so there is a risk adjuster return,
we will not give you a risk, all risk
premium product, invest, we will beat
inflation, we will get
good returns in the long term perspective
I will create a bill and
I will get a return of 4.9%, but I can
tell the media that then with this we will
collect alternatives, what are the
comparisons, we will now see,
for example,
how good returns can this nice of products give you, we
want to invest with a combination of term insurance because it looks possible,
you have to give a term cover also,
so term and show investment work, from that the
balance amount is ₹150000,
that too for 50 years, but
how much you will get, 40.68%, you get
show returns 1% and some other returns will be,
you get
such a good, very huge different,
so it is a risk free product,
for example, like mixed fund, these
legis mutual funds also, we want to invest in term
insurance plus our assistant
combination, if you inverse the
most positive term 10 years, then
you
get 58.96% in the end, that too less, that too 12%  If
we take up CAGR, then if we cross the long term mark of 7% for
7 years, then the
SEC long term investment, till now if you
see the fast track record of this fund then it is
delivering up to 12%, so we get an ADAM return of
58.96 lakhs and if you look at the post tax return, then
also 56.16 lakhs, many sir, see the ICICI
Prudential, it gives you better returns than
inflation, gives returns of
risk and just the right returns, so this
is the product in the screen, compact you can do it well for
Elite Life,
so finally whether to take up a
long term commitment, you would have
tested your tolerance, you can
invest in insurance policies, you can do
one or two, I mean this is the third
combination and you can also do term loan and PF,
this is possible, compare
these
products, you will get long term, so if
we are not able to invest in this fund then I
avoid it, because it will not give long term,
so you can definitely comment,
so definitely block us on our website,
its link is in our description.  You
can watch and I hope you
liked this video, if so then like, share
and subscribe to the YouTube channel and if you have
no doubts about having a van-on-van discussion
then
you can definitely book a complimentary financial consultation with our certified financial planner
and Abhi says that
financial planning is not personal finance but
investment choices but
directly shares the knowledge and experience of industry experts
whose registration link can also be
described, so I hope you liked
this video and it would have benefited you, I hope so
under the next
video, thank you.